import { MemoCard } from "@/types/app"

export const spanishCards: MemoCard[] = [
  {
    id: "1",
    title: "Desayuno",
    front: "Desayuno",
    back: "Breakfast",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    title: "Almuerzo",
    front: "Almuerzo",
    back: "Lunch",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    title: "Cena",
    front: "Cena",
    back: "Dinner",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    title: "Antes",
    front: "Antes",
    back: "Before",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    title: "Después",
    front: "Después",
    back: "After",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    title: "Entender",
    front: "Entender Yo entiendo Tú entiendes",
    back: "To understand, I understand, you understand.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    title: "Hacer",
    front: "Hacer Yo hago Tú haces",
    back: "To do, I do, you do.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    title: "Poder",
    front: "Poder Yo puedo Tú puedes",
    back: "To be able, I can, you can.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    title: "Ver",
    front: "Ver Yo veo Tú ves",
    back: "To see, I see, you see.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    title: "Volver",
    front: "Volver Yo vuelvo Tú vuelves",
    back: "To return, I return, you return.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    title: "Ir",
    front: "Ir Yo voy Tú vas",
    back: "To go, I go, you go.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    title: "Decir",
    front: "Decir Yo digo Tú dices",
    back: "To say, I say, you say.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    title: "Dar",
    front: "Dar Yo doy Tú das",
    back: "To give, I give, you give.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    title: "Escuchar",
    front: "Escuchar Yo escucho Tú escuchas",
    back: "To listen, I listen, you listen.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    title: "Ser",
    front: "Ser Yo soy Tú eres",
    back: "To be, I am, you are.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "16",
    title: "Abrir",
    front: "Abrir Yo abro Tú abres",
    back: "To open, I open, you open.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "17",
    title: "Cerrar",
    front: "Cerrar Yo cierro Tú cierras",
    back: "To close, I close, you close.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "19",
    title: "Creer",
    front: "Creer Yo creo Tú crees",
    back: "To believe, I believe, you believe.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "20",
    title: "Comer",
    front: "Comer Yo como Tú comes",
    back: "To eat, I eat, you eat.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "21",
    title: "Beber",
    front: "Beber Yo bebo Tú bebes",
    back: "To drink, I drink, you drink.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "22",
    title: "Dormir",
    front: "Dormir Yo duermo Tú duermes",
    back: "To sleep, I sleep, you sleep.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "23",
    title: "Jugar",
    front: "Jugar Yo juego Tú juegas",
    back: "To play, I play, you play.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "24",
    title: "Saber",
    front: "Saber Yo sé Tú sabes",
    back: "To know, I know, you know.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "25",
    title: "Manejar",
    front: "Manejar Yo manejo Tú manejas",
    back: "To drive, I drive, you drive.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "26",
    title: "Conocer",
    front: "Conocer Yo conozco Tú conoces",
    back: "To know (people), I know, you know.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "27",
    title: "Cantar",
    front: "Cantar Yo canto Tú cantas",
    back: "To sing, I sing, you sing.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "28",
    title: "Lengua",
    front: "Lengua",
    back: "Language",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "29",
    title: "Palabra",
    front: "Palabra",
    back: "Word",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "30",
    title: "Mas",
    front: "Mas",
    back: "More",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "31",
    title: "Menos",
    front: "Menos",
    back: "Less",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "32",
    title: "Avión",
    front: "Avión",
    back: "Airplane",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "33",
    title: "Mejor",
    front: "Mejor",
    back: "Better",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "34",
    title: "Peor",
    front: "Peor",
    back: "Worse",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "35",
    title: "Listo",
    front: "Listo",
    back: "Ready",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "36",
    title: "Llegar",
    front: "Llegar Yo llego Tú llegas",
    back: "To arrive, I arrive, you arrive.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "37",
    title: "Caliente",
    front: "Caliente",
    back: "Hot",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "38",
    title: "Sitio",
    front: "Sitio",
    back: "Place",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "39",
    title: "Ojo",
    front: "Ojo",
    back: "Eye",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "40",
    title: "Nariz",
    front: "Nariz",
    back: "Nose",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "41",
    title: "Boca",
    front: "Boca",
    back: "Mouth",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "42",
    title: "Cabeza",
    front: "Cabeza",
    back: "Head",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "43",
    title: "Llevar",
    front: "Llevar Yo llevo Tú llevas",
    back: "To carry, I carry, you carry.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "44",
    title: "Lavar",
    front: "Lavar Yo lavo Tú lavas",
    back: "To wash, I wash, you wash.",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "45",
    title: "Bolsa",
    front: "Bolsa",
    back: "Bag",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "46",
    title: "Papa",
    front: "Papa",
    back: "Potato",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "47",
    title: "Platano",
    front: "Platano",
    back: "Banana",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "48",
    title: "Fresa",
    front: "Fresa",
    back: "Strawberry",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "49",
    title: "Llave",
    front: "Llave",
    back: "Key",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "50",
    title: "Cuchara",
    front: "Cuchara",
    back: "Spoon",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "51",
    title: "Tenedor",
    front: "Tenedor",
    back: "Fork",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "52",
    title: "Cuchillo",
    front: "Cuchillo",
    back: "Knife",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "53",
    title: "Mesa",
    front: "Mesa",
    back: "Table",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "54",
    title: "Silla",
    front: "Silla",
    back: "Chair",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "55",
    title: "Ventana",
    front: "Ventana",
    back: "Window",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "56",
    title: "Puerta",
    front: "Puerta",
    back: "Door",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "57",
    title: "Pared",
    front: "Pared",
    back: "Wall",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "58",
    title: "Techo",
    front: "Techo",
    back: "Roof",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "59",
    title: "Piso",
    front: "Piso",
    back: "Floor",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "60",
    title: "Cielo",
    front: "Cielo",
    back: "Sky",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "61",
    title: "Mar",
    front: "Mar",
    back: "Sea",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "62",
    title: "Río",
    front: "Río",
    back: "River",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "63",
    title: "Lago",
    front: "Lago",
    back: "Lake",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "64",
    title: "Montaña",
    front: "Montaña",
    back: "Mountain",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "65",
    title: "Bosque",
    front: "Bosque",
    back: "Forest",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "66",
    title: "Playa",
    front: "Playa",
    back: "Beach",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "67",
    title: "Sol",
    front: "Sol",
    back: "Sun",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "68",
    title: "Luna",
    front: "Luna",
    back: "Moon",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "69",
    title: "Estrella",
    front: "Estrella",
    back: "Star",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "70",
    title: "Nube",
    front: "Nube",
    back: "Cloud",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "71",
    title: "Lluvia",
    front: "Lluvia",
    back: "Rain",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "72",
    title: "Nieve",
    front: "Nieve",
    back: "Snow",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "73",
    title: "Viento",
    front: "Viento",
    back: "Wind",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "74",
    title: "Frío",
    front: "Frío",
    back: "Cold",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "75",
    title: "Calor",
    front: "Calor",
    back: "Heat",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "76",
    title: "Templado",
    front: "Templado",
    back: "Warm",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "77",
    title: "Templo",
    front: "Templo",
    back: "Temple",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "78",
    title: "Iglesia",
    front: "Iglesia",
    back: "Church",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "79",
    title: "Mezquita",
    front: "Mezquita",
    back: "Mosque",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
  {
    id: "80",
    title: "Sinagoga",
    front: "Sinagoga",
    back: "Synagogue",
    category: "Español",
    level: 0,
    lastPracticeTimestamp: "",
    createdAtTimestamp: "",
    useReversedDefaultView: false,
  },
]
